A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 1, Accession 1 FA772
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Exchanges - General, 2
  - Ms.CHEN Xiaoying (Changzhou No.1 Middle School), 2001-2002 (Box 131, Folder 1798)
    Benjamin Banneker Academy, District 13, Brooklyn, NY.
  - Ms.CHEN Xiaoying (Changzhou No.1 Middle School), 2001-2002 (Box 140A, Folder 1798A)
  - Ms. CHEN Xuemei (Inner Mongolia Teachers University Affiliated Middle School), 1996-1997 (Box 131, Folder 1799)
    Nederland High School, Nederland, CO.
  - Ms. CHEN Yanping (Hefei No.2 Middle School), 2004-2005 (Box 131, Folder 1800)
    Milwaukee School of Languages, Milwaukee, WI.
  - Ms. CHEN Yiqi (Jianghan Oil Field Foreign Language School), 2011-2012 (Box 131, Folder 1801)
    Fort Gibson, OK.
  - Ms. CHEN Yiqi (Jianghan Oil Field Foreign Language School), 2011-2012 (Box 140A, Folder 1801A)
  - Ms. CHEN Zhiyun (Nanjing No.29 Middle School), 2002-2003 (Box 131, Folder 1802)
    Fort Collins, CO.
  - Ms. CHENG Songmei (Anqing No.1 Middle School), 2013-2014 (Box 131, Folder 1803)
    Sallisaw, OK.
  - Ms. CHENG Songmei (Anqing No.1 Middle School), 2013-2014 (Box 140A, Folder 1803A)
  - Ms. CUI Qunfeng (Jixi No.16 Middle School), 2006-2007 (Box 131, Folder 1804)
    Emerson Elementary School, Tulsa, OK.
  - Mr. CUI Xianwen (Tongling No.3 Middle School), 2003-2004 (Box 131, Folder 1805)
  - Ms. DA Wei'na (Lu'an No. 2 Middle School, Anhui), 2012-2013 (Box 131, Folder 1806)
    Grimes Elementary School, Tulsa, OK.
  - Ms. DA Wei'na (Lu'an No. 2 Middle School, Anhui), 2012-2013 (Box 140A, Folder 1806A)
  - Ms. DAI Lin (Suzhou No. 4 Middle School), 2004-2005 (Box 131, Folder 1807)
  - Ms. DAI Qinghua (Yangzhou University Affiliated Middle School), 2002-2003 (Box 131, Folder 1808)
  - Ms. DENG Xiaojin (Suzhou Middle School), 1997-1998 (Box 132, Folder 1809)
    Beacon School, New York City. File includes correspondence from DENG during and following her visit.
  - Ms. DONG Jingchun (Changqing No. 2 Middle School), 2006-2007 (Box 132, Folder 1810)
  - Ms. DONG Qimei (Suzhou No. 1 Middle School), 1999-2000 (Box 132, Folder 1811)
  - Ms. DONG Qimei (Suzhou No. 1 Middle School), 1999-2000; FA772:079; Still Image (Box 148, Folder 1811)
    2 snapshots
  - Ms. DONG Shuhua (Changzhou Senior Middle School), 2001-2002 (Box 132, Folder 1812)
  - Ms. DONG Shuhua (Changzhou Senior Middle School), 2001-2002; FA772:080; Still Image (Box 148, Folder 1812)
    2 snapshots, including image of teachers with two students wrapped in tiger skins (?).
  - Ms. DU Min (Hefei No. 1 Middle School), 2005-2006 (Box 132, Folder 1813)
  - Ms. DU Ruirui (Heilongjiang Provincial Experimental High School), 2009-2010 (Box 132, Folder 1814)
  - Ms. DU Ruirui (Heilongjiang Provincial Experimental High School), 2009-2010 (Box 140A, Folder 1814A)
  - Ms. FAN Duoxia (Xinhua Middle School, Yangshou), 2002-2003 (Box 132, Folder 1815)
  - Ms. FAN Duoxia (Xinhua Middle School, Yangshou), 2002-2003; FA772:081; Still Image (Box 148, Folder 1815)
    3 snapshots from Florida trip, including one image of FAN.
  - Ms. FAN Minli (Xi'an Foreign Language School), 2004-2005 (Box 132, Folder 1816)
    Holland Hall School, Tulsa, OK.
  - Ms. FAN Yan (Yangzhou Middle School), 2006-2007 (Box 132, Folder 1817)
  - Mr. FANG Qing (Nanjing Foreign Language School), 2011-2012 (Box 132, Folder 1818)
  - Ms. FENG Wei (Xinhua Middle School, Yangzhou), 2003-2004 (Box 132, Folder 1819)
  - Ms. FENG Yujuan (Hefei No. 1 Middle School), 2004-2005 (Box 132, Folder 1820)
  - Ms. FENG Zhiyun (Suzhou No. 10 Middle School), 2001-2002 (Box 132, Folder 1821)
  - Ms. FENG Zhiyun (Suzhou No. 10 Middle School), 2001-2002; FA772:082; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1821)
    2 snapshots of FENG with host family.
  - Ms. FU Hong (Beijing No. 8 High School, Yihai Branch), 2012-2013 (Box 132, Folder 1822)
    Whitman-Hanson Regional School District (Boston, MA).
  - Ms. FU Hong (Beijing No. 8 High School, Yihai Branch), 2012-2013 (Box 140A, Folder 1822A)
  - Mr. FU Zhanjun (Wenhui Middle School, Beijing), 2006-2007 (Box 132, Folder 1823)
  - Ms. GAO Changcui (Nanjing No. 29 Middle School), 2003-2004 (Box 132, Folder 1824)
    Garden School, Queens, NY.
  - Ms. GAO Chengchun (Suzhou No. 4 Middle School), 2002-2003 (Box 132, Folder 1825)
    Bangor Public Schools, Bangor, ME.
  - Ms. GAO Chengchun (Suzhou No. 4 Middle School), 2002-2003; FA772:083; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1825)
    2 snapshots of GAO teaching and classroom phrases poster.
  - Mr. GAO Jianwei (Xi'an Jiaotong University Affiliated Middle School), 2008-2009 (Box 132, Folder 1826)
  - Mr. GAO Jianwei (Xi'an Jiaotong University Affiliated Middle School), 2008-2009 (Box 140A, Folder 1826A)
  - Ms. GAO Weiyun (Nanshida Fuzhong / Nanjing Teachers University Affiliated Middle School), 2004-2005 (Box 132, Folder 1827)
  - Ms. GAO Xing (Beijing No. 94 Middle School), 2004-2005 (Box 132, Folder 1828)
  - Ms. GAO Yang (Wenhua Road Primary School, Shenyang), 2010-2011 (Box 132, Folder 1829)
  - Ms. GAO Yang (Wenhua Road Primary School, Shenyang), 2010-2011 (Box 140A, Folder 1829A)
  - Ms. GENG Wen (Changzhou No. 3 Middle School), 2001-2002 (Box 132, Folder 1830)
  - Ms. GONG Aiping (Jiangdu Middle School), 2007-2008 (Box 132, Folder 1831)
    Stamford, CT.
  - Ms. GONG Aiping (Jiangdu Middle School), 2007-2008 (Box 140A, Folder 1831A)
  - Ms. GONG Yan (Nanjing Normal University Affiliated Middle School), 2001-2002 (Box 132, Folder 1832)
  - Mr. GUAN Jigang (Luoyang Foreign Language School), 1999-2000 (Box 132, Folder 1833)
  - Mr. GUAN Jigang (Luoyang Foreign Language School), 1999-2000; FA772:084; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1833)
    2 snapshots of family and exchange teacher (s?) at dinner table.
  - Ms. GUAN Yi (Suzhou Middle School), 1996-1997 (Box 132, Folder 1834)
    District 25, Flushing, Queens, NY.
  - Ms. GUO Li (Anshan No. 1 Middle School), 2011-2012 (Box 132, Folder 1835)
    File contains only the application.
  - Ms. GUO Limiao (Luoyang No. 2 Foreign Language School), 2006-2007 (Box 132, Folder 1836)
  - Ms. GUO Xiaoling (Luoyang Foreign Language School), 2008-2009 (Box 132, Folder 1837)
  - Mr. GUO Yi (Xinhua Middle School, Yangzhou), 2000-2001 (Box 132, Folder 1838)
  - Mr. GUO Yi (Xinhua Middle School, Yangzhou), 2000-2001; FA772:085; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1838)
    Includes 7 snapshots of GUO with other exchange teachers and family(?), 2000-2004.
  - Ms. GUO Ying (Beijing No. 96 Middle School), 2012-2013 (Box 132, Folder 1839)
  - Ms. GUO Ying (Beijing No. 96 Middle School), 2012-2013 (Box 140A, Folder 1839A)
  - Ms. GUO Zhijie (Beijing No. 12 Middle School), 1998-1999 (Box 132, Folder 1840)
    P.S. 163, New York.
  - Ms. GUO Zhijie (Beijing No. 12 Middle School), 1998-1999; FA772:086; Still Image (Box 148, Folder 1840)
    6 snapshots of GUO with students and others, including photos of student artwork.
  - Ms. HAN Aimin (Dailan No. 8 Middle School), 2006-2007 (Box 132, Folder 1841)
  - Mr. HAN Bangsheng (Hefei No. 6 Middle School), 2008-2009 (Box 132, Folder 1842)
  - Ms. HAN Dongni (Nanjing Foreign Language School), 2009-2010 (Box 132, Folder 1843)
    Hoover Elementary School, Tulsa, OK.
  - Ms. HAN Dongni (Nanjing Foreign Language School), 2009-2010 (Box 140A, Folder 1843A)
  - Ms. HAO Yuanjun (Fengtai Experimental School), 1996-1997 (Box 132, Folder 1844)
    Boulder, CO.
  - Mr. HAO Zhiyong (Beishida Experimental Middle School), 2004-2005 (Box 132, Folder 1845)
    Edison Preparatory School, Tulsa, OK.
  - Mr. HAO Zhiyong (Beishida Experimental Middle School), 2004-2005 (Box 140A, Folder 1845A)
  - Mr. HE Dongliang (Nanjing Foreign Language School), 2003-2004 (Box 133, Folder 1846)
    Brookline High School, Brookline, MA.
  - Mr. HE Yeming (Hefei No. 1 Middle School), 2008-2009 (Box 133, Folder 1847)
  - Mr. HE Yeming (Hefei No. 1 Middle School), 2008-2009 (Box 140A, Folder 1847A)
  - Ms. HOU Fengyan (Nanjing No. 29 Middle School), 2010-2011 (Box 133, Folder 1848)
    Staples High School, Westport, CT.
  - Ms. HOU Fengyan (Nanjing No. 29 Middle School), 2010-2011 (Box 140A, Folder 1848A)
  - Mr. HOU Jisheng (Fengtai Experimental School), 1997-1998 (Box 133, Folder 1849)
  - Mr. HOU Jisheng (Fengtai Experimental School), 1997-1998; FA772:087; Still Image (Box 148, Folder 1849)
    6 snapshots of classes and photo displays; cut negatives of other images.
  - Mr. HOU Jisheng (Fengtai Experimental School), 1997-1998 (Box 140A, Folder 1849A)
  - Ms. HU Muxia (Luhe Middle School), 2004-2005 (Box 133, Folder 1850)
  - Ms. HU Muxia (Luhe Middle School), 2004-2005 (Box 140A, Folder 1850A)
  - Ms. HU Wei (Nanjing No. 29 Middle School), 2005-2006 (Box 133, Folder 1851)
  - Ms. HU Yingjie (Beijing No. 94 Middle School), 2003-2004 (Box 133, Folder 1852)
  - Ms. HU Yingjie (Beijing No. 94 Middle School), 2003-2004 (Box 140A, Folder 1852A)
  - Ms. HUA Fang (Xinhua Middle School, Yangzhou), 2001-2002 (Box 133, Folder 1853)
  - Ms. HUA Fang (Xinhua Middle School, Yangzhou), 2001-2002; FA772:088; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1853)
    2 snapshots of children drinking tea (with essay).
  - Ms. HUA Fang (Xinhua Middle School, Yangzhou), 2001-2002 (Box 140A, Folder 1853A)
  - Mr. HUANG Gaosheng (Beijiao Middle School), 1998-1999 (Box 133, Folder 1854)
    Science Skills Center High School, New York.
  - Ms. HUANG Guoqin (Luoyang Foreign Language School), 2001-2002 (Box 133, Folder 1855)
  - Ms. HUANG Haibing (Hefei No. 168 Middle School), 2009-2010 (Box 133, Folder 1856)
  - Ms. HUANG Jinjin (Hefei No.2 Middle School), 2008-2009 (Box 133, Folder 1857)
    Lee's Summit, MO.
  - Ms. HUANG Jun (Yangzhou University Affiliated Middle School), 2004-2005 (Box 133, Folder 1858)
  - Mr. HUANG Xichang (Tongling No. 1 Middle School), 2003-2004 (Box 133, Folder 1859)
  - Mr. HUANG Yakan (Suzhou No. 3 Middle School), 1998-1999 (Box 133, Folder 1860)
  - Mr. HUANG Yakan (Suzhou No. 3 Middle School), 1998-1999; FA772:089; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1860)
    Snapshots: Huang in Mississippi; with host family; in Boston, National Day celebration; with students and others.
  - Ms. JI Chunhong (Yangzhou Middle School), 1997-1998 (Box 133, Folder 1861)
  - Ms. JI Min (Nanjing Foreign Language School), 2013-2014 (Box 133, Folder 1862)
    Owasso High School, Owasso, OK.
  - Ms. JI Min (Nanjing Foreign Language School), 2013-2014 (Box 140A, Folder 1862A)
  - Mr. JIANG Lifeng (Xi'an Jiaotong University Affiliated Middle School), 2010-2011 (Box 133, Folder 1863)
  - Mr. JIANG Lifeng (Xi'an Jiaotong University Affiliated Middle School), 2010-2011 (Box 140A, Folder 1863A)
  - Ms. JIANG Mingzhen (Acheng No. 1 High School), 2006-2007 (Box 133, Folder 1864)
  - Ms. JIANG Qin (Suzhou No. 10 Middle School), 2003-2004 (Box 133, Folder 1865)
  - Mr. JIANG Qizhong (Anqing No. 1 Middle School, Anhui), 2006-2007 (Box 133, Folder 1866)
  - Ms. JIANG Ye (Shijiazhuang No. 42 Middle School), 2013-2014 (Box 133, Folder 1867)
  - Ms. JIANG Ye (Shijiazhuang No. 42 Middle School), 2013-2014 (Box 140A, Folder 1867A)
  - Mr. JIANG Yongmin (Suzhou No. 1 Middle School), 2002-2003 (Box 133, Folder 1868)
  - Mr. JIN Dongping (Hefei No. 6 Middle School), 2005-2006 (Box 133, Folder 1869)
  - Mr. JIN Dongping (Hefei No. 6 Middle School), 2005-2006 (Box 140A, Folder 1869A)
  - Ms. JIN Mei (Beijing No. 2 Experimental Primary School), 2012-2013 (Box 133, Folder 1870)
    Edgewood Elementary School, New Haven, CT.
  - Ms. JIN Mei (Beijing No. 2 Experimental Primary School), 2012-2013 (Box 140A, Folder 1870A)
  - Ms. JIN Xuemei (Suzhou No. 6 Middle School), 2008-2009 (Box 133, Folder 1871)
  - Mr. JIN Zhongming (Suzhou High School-SIP), 2006-2007 (Box 133, Folder 1872)
    Chaparral High School, Douglas County, CO.
  - Ms. KANG Xia (Yangzhou Teachers University Affiliated Middle School), 1998-1999 (Box 133, Folder 1873)
  - Ms. KANG Xia (Yangzhou Teachers University Affiliated Middle School), 1998-1999 (Box 140A, Folder 1873A)
  - Mr. KONG Qingke (Nanjing No. 9 Middle School), 2011-2012 (Box 133, Folder 1874)
    Whitman-Hanson Regional School District, Whitman, MA.
  - Mr. KONG Qingke (Nanjing No. 9 Middle School), 2011-2012 (Box 133, Folder 1874)
  - Mr. KONG Qingke (Nanjing No. 9 Middle School), 2011-2012 (Box 140A, Folder 1874A)
  - Ms. KONG Yanjun (Fengtai Experimental School), 1998-1999 (Box 133, Folder 1875)
    Harvard-Kent School, Boston, MA.
  - Ms. KONG Yanjun (Fengtai Experimental School), 1998-1999; FA772:090; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1875)
    9 snapshots from various occasions.
  - Ms. KONG Yanjun (Fengtai Experimental School), 1998-1999 (Box 140A, Folder 1875A)
  - Ms. LAN Hui (Nanjing Foreign Language School), 2012-2013 (Box 133, Folder 1876)
    McKinley and Cleveland Elementary schools, Norman, OK.
  - Ms. LAN Hui (Nanjing Foreign Language School), 2012-2013 (Box 140A, Folder 1876A)
  - Ms. LEI Jiaduan (Chengdu No. 7 Middle School), 1996-1997 (Box 133, Folder 1877)
  - Ms. LEI Jiaduan (Chengdu No. 7 Middle School), 1996-1997; FA772:091; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1877)
    3 snapshots of Lei and her classroom.
  - Ms. LEI Yan (Beijing No. 8 Middle School, Yihai Branch), 2012-2013 (Box 133, Folder 1878)
    Davis School, Brockton, MA.
  - Ms. LEI Yan (Beijing No. 8 Middle School, Yihai Branch), 2012-2013 (Box 140A, Folder 1878A)
  - Ms. LI Baoping (Huiwen Middle School), 1998-1999 (Box 133, Folder 1879)
    Belmont High School, Belmont, MA.
  - Ms. LI Baoping (Huiwen Middle School), 1998-1999; FA772:092; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1879)
    9 snapshots of National Day (Boston) and Arlington Day; host family and house.
  - Ms. LI Caixia (Luoyang No. 2 Foreign Language School), 2002-2003 (Box 133, Folder 1880)
  - Mr. LI Chong (Mianyang Middle School), 2008-2009 (Box 133, Folder 1881)
  - Ms. LI Hongxia (Xi'an Foreign Language School), 2004-2005 (Box 133, Folder 1882)
  - Ms. LI Hui (Beijing No. 15 Middle School), 2000-2001 (Box 134, Folder 1883)
  - Ms. LI Hui (Beijing No. 15 Middle School), 2000-2001; FA772:093; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1883)
    Snapshots of Lui and her colleagues and classes.
  - Ms. LI Li (Hefei No. 7 Middle School), 2008-2009 (Box 134, Folder 1884)
    Cascia Hall School, Tulsa, OK.
  - Ms. LI Li (Hefei No. 7 Middle School), 2008-2009 (Box 140A, Folder 1884A)
  - Ms. LI Rongjie (Dailan No. 48 Middle School), 2004-2005 (Box 134, Folder 1885)
  - Ms. LI Rongjie (Dailan No. 48 Middle School), 2004-2005 (Box 140A, Folder 1885A)
  - Ms. Li Sulian (Suzhou No. 10 Middle School), 2000-2001 (Box 134, Folder 1886)
  - Ms. Li Sulian (Suzhou No. 10 Middle School), 2000-2001; FA772:094; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1886)
    4 snapshots of Li making dumplings for her class.
  - Ms. LI Xiao (Luoyang Foreign Language School), 2007-2008 (Box 134, Folder 1887)
  - Ms. LI Xiaowen (Hefei No.1 Middle School), 2007-2008 (Box 134, Folder 1888)
  - Ms. LI Xiumei (Inner Mongolia Teachers University Affiliated Middle School), 1998-1999 (Box 134, Folder 1889)
    Quabbin Regional School District, MA.
  - Ms. LI Xiumei (Inner Mongolia Teachers University Affiliated Middle School), 1998-1999; FA772:095; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1889)
    3 snapshots of LI at graduation and in classroom.
  - Mr. LI Xuede (Yan'am Middle School), 2007-2008 (Box 134, Folder 1890)
  - Mr. LI Xuede (Yan'am Middle School), 2007-2008 (Box 140A, Folder 1890A)
  - Mr. LI Yingjun (Nanjing Foreign Language School), 2000-2001 (Box 134, Folder 1891)
  - Mr. LI Yingjun (Nanjing Foreign Language School), 2000-2001; FA772:096; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1891)
    13 snapshots of students' Chinese festival.
  - Ms. LI Yuehui (Shijiazhuang No. 42 Middle School), 2008-2009 (Box 134, Folder 1892)
  - Mr. LI Yuemin (Luoyang No. 2 Foreign Language School), 2007-2008 (Box 134, Folder 1893)
  - Mr. LI Yuepeng (Hefei No. 7 Middle School), 2009-2010 (Box 134, Folder 1894)
  - Mr. LI Yuepeng (Hefei No. 7 Middle School), 2009-2010 (Box 140A, Folder 1894A)
  - Ms. LIANG Feng (Luoyang No. 2 Foreign Language School), 2003-2004, 2008-2009 (Box 134, Folder 1895)
    Liang taught in La Crosse, WI, in 2008-2009. The file also includes her application for 2003-2004.
  - Ms. LIANG Gemei (Remin University Affiiliated Primary School), 2012-2013 (Box 134, Folder 1896)
  - Ms. LIANG Gemei (Remin University Affiiliated Primary School), 2012-2013 (Box 140A, Folder 1896A)
  - Ms. LIANG Hua (Dalian No. 8 Middle School), 1999-2000 (Box 134, Folder 1897)
  - Ms. LIANG Yaping (Huiwen Middle School), 1999-2000 (Box 134, Folder 1898)
    District 13, Brooklyn, NY.
  - Ms. LIU Hong (Dalian No. 23 Middle School), 2002-2003 (Box 134, Folder 1899)
  - Ms. LIU Hong (Dalian No. 23 Middle School), 2002-2003; FA772:097; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1899)
    1 snapshot of Margot Landman with unidentified group of Chinese.
  - Ms. LIU Jianying (Ma'anshan No. 2 Middle School), 2010-2011 (Box 134, Folder 1900)
  - Ms. LIU Jianying (Ma'anshan No. 2 Middle School), 2010-2011 (Box 140A, Folder 1900A)
  - Ms. LIU Jinsong (Beijing No. 15 Middle School), 1999-2000 (Box 134, Folder 1901)
    Lower East Side Preparatory High School, New York City.
  - Ms. LIU Jinsong (Beijing No. 15 Middle School), 1999-2000; FA772:098; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1901)
    2 snapshots of Liu with teacher and students.
  - Ms. LIU Junhong (Suzhou No. 10 Middle School), 2002-2003 (Box 134, Folder 1902)
  - Ms. LIU Junhong (Suzhou No. 10 Middle School), 2002-2003; FA772:099; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1902)
    4 snapshots of classroom and Liu.
  - Ms. LIU Junhong (Suzhou No. 10 Middle School), 2002-2003 (Box 140A, Folder 1902A)
  - Ms. LIU Junling (Beijing No. 12 Middle School), 1999-2000 (Box 134, Folder 1903)
    Staples High School, Westport, CT. File includes landscape photo of Westport in spring (photo retained in file and not separated).
  - Ms. LIU Junling (Beijing No. 12 Middle School), 1999-2000 (Box 140A, Folder 1903A)
  - Ms. LIU Kun (Beijing No. 15 Middle School), 1999-2000 (Box 134, Folder 1904)
  - Ms. LIU Kun (Beijing No. 15 Middle School), 1999-2000; FA772:100; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1904)
    12 snapshots of Liu and others.
  - Ms. LIU Manxiang (Beijing No. 14 Middle School), 2001-2002 (Box 134, Folder 1905)
    Legacy High School, Manhattan, NY.
  - Mr. LIU Renjie (Yangzhou Middle School), 2003-2004 (Box 134, Folder 1906)
  - Mr. LIU Wei (Huiwen Middle School), 1999-2000 (Box 134, Folder 1907)
    New York City.
  - Mr. LIU Wei (Huiwen Middle School), 1999-2000; FA772:101; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1907)
    1 snapshot of Liu and Margot Landman at NYC restaurant, October 1999.
  - Ms. LIU Wen (Beijing No. 94 Middle School), 2005-2006 (Box 134, Folder 1908)
    Beacon School, New York City.
  - Ms. LIU Wenhui (Dalian No. 1 Middle School), 2003-2004 (Box 134, Folder 1909)
  - Ms. LIU Xianghong (Dalian No. 24 Middle School), 1996-1997 (Box 134, Folder 1910)
    PS 24, Flushing, NY. Liu was initially assigned to the Beacon School, New York City.
  - Ms. LIU Xianghong (Dalian No. 24 Middle School), 1996-1997; FA772:102; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1910)
    9 Snapshots of trip to Disneyland and elsewhere; 2 snapshots of Liu (?) with Margot Landman and another Chinese woman.
  - Ms. LIU Xingshi (Dalian No. 23 Middle School), 2003-2004 (Box 134, Folder 1911)
  - Ms. LIU Yan (Yangzhou Middle School), 2005-2006 (Box 134, Folder 1912)
  - Ms. LIU Yan (Yangzhou Middle School), 2005-2006; FA772:103; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1912)
    1 snapshot of Liu in language lab.
  - Ms. LIU Yanling (Dalian No. 1 Middle School), 1998-1999 (Box 134, Folder 1913)
    West Middle School, Denver, CO.
  - Ms. LIU Yanling (Dalian No. 1 Middle School), 1998-1999; FA772:104; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1913)
    9 captioned snapshots of Liu at school and with hosts.
  - Ms. LIU Yingsu (Inner Mongolia Teachers University Affiliated Middle School), 1997-1998 (Box 134, Folder 1914)
    Boulder Valley School District, Boulder, CO.
  - Ms. LIU Yingsu (Inner Mongolia Teachers University Affiliated Middle School), 1997-1998; FA772:105; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1914)
    1 snapshot of Liu and Margot Landman.
  - Ms. LU Lingma (Beijao Middle School, Changzhou), 1997-1998 (Box 134, Folder 1915)
  - Ms. LU Yuan (Renmin University Affiliated High School), 2006-2007 (Box 135, Folder 1916)
  - Mr. LU Xiaochen (Suzhou Middle School), 1996-1997 (Box 135, Folder 1917)
  - Mr. LU Xiaochen (Suzhou Middle School), 1996-1997; FA772:106; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1917)
    Wedding photos (2), and snapshots of Forbidden City and China (borrowed from and to be returned to Michael Holzman, 1997).
  - Ms. LUO Jinxin (Nanshida Affiliated Middle School), 2002-2003 (Box 135, Folder 1918)
  - Ms. LUO Jinxin (Nanshida Affiliated Middle School), 2002-2003; FA772:107; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1918)
    4 snapshots of Luo teaching and with Margot Landman.
  - Ms. MA Chenghong (Wuhu No. 1 Middle School), 2007-2008 (Box 135, Folder 1919)
  - Ms. MA Yan (Nanjing Foreign Language School), 2006-2007 (Box 135, Folder 1920)
  - Ms. MA Yihui (Beijing No. 94 Middle School), 2002-2003 (Box 135, Folder 1921)
  - Ms. MA Yihui (Beijing No. 94 Middle School), 2002-2003; FA772:108; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1921)
    5 snapshots of Ma teaching.
  - MA Yuming (Suzhou No. 1 Middle School), 1999-2000 (Box 135, Folder 1922)
  - Ms. MENG Xianglian (Qingdao No. 58 Middle School), 2010-2011 (Box 135, Folder 1923)
  - Ms. MENG Xianglian (Qingdao No. 58 Middle School), 2010-2011 (Box 140A, Folder 1923A)
  - Ms. MIN Wei (Dalian No. 23 Middle School), 1997-1998 (Box 135, Folder 1924)
    PS 22, District 25, Flushing, NY.
  - Mr. NI Jintao (Hefei No. 1 Middle School), 2008-2009 (Box 135, Folder 1925)
  - Mr. NI Qingrong (Jinling High School, Nanjing), 2006-2007 (Box 135, Folder 1926)
  - Ms. NING Guili (Beijing No. 15 Middle School), 2001-2002 (Box 135, Folder 1927)
  - Ms. NING Guili (Beijing No. 15 Middle School), 2001-2002; FA772:109; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1927)
    2 snapshots with Margot Landman.
  - Ms. PAN Huali (Caoqiao Experimental Middle School), 2009-2010 (Box 135, Folder 1928)
  - Ms. QIAN Jianfen (Suzhou No. 1 Middle School), 2000-2001 (Box 135, Folder 1929)
  - Ms. QIAN Jianfen (Suzhou No. 1 Middle School), 2000-2001; FA772:110; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1929)
    10 snapshots of Chinese night; 11 other photos of Qian in classroom and with friends.
  - Ms. QIAO Feng (Yangzhou University Affiliated Middle School), 2005-2006 (Box 135, Folder 1930)
  - Ms. QIN Hong (Beijing No. 55 Middle School), 2005-2006 (Box 135, Folder 1931)
  - Ms. QIN Wei (Luoyang No. 2 Foreign Language School), 2011-2012 (Box 135, Folder 1932)
  - Ms. QIN Xiangqing (Luoyang Foreign Language School), 2000-2001 (Box 135, Folder 1933)
  - Ms. QIN Xiangqing (Luoyang Foreign Language School), 2000-2001; FA772:111; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1933)
    5 snapshots of Qin in classroom and with others.
  - Mr. RUAN Hangwei (Changzhou No.1 Middle School), 1996-1997 (Box 135, Folder 1934)
    Grover Cleveland High School, Queens, NY.
  - Mr. RUAN Hangwei (Changzhou No.1 Middle School), 1996-1997 (Box 140A, Folder 1934A)
  - Ms. SHANG Yuanyuan (Nanjing Foreign Language School), 2007-2008 (Box 135, Folder 1935)
    Royal Oak, MI.
  - Ms. SHANG Yuanyuan (Nanjing Foreign Language School), 2007-2008; FA772:112; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1935)
    2 photos of Shang and family.
  - Ms. SHEN Xiaojin (Beijing No. 12 Middle School), 1997-1998 (Box 135, Folder 1936)
    Cambridge, MA.
  - Ms. SHEN Xiaojin (Beijing No. 12 Middle School), 1997-1998; FA772:113; Still image (Box 148, Folder 1936)
    1 snapshot of Shen leading stretching exercises at Chinese New Year's celebration.
  - Ms. SHI Suping (Dalian Experimental Middle School), 1997-1998 (Box 135, Folder 1937)
    Tottenville High School, Staten Island, NY. File includes extensive correspondence, copies of student paintings and calligraphy, and copies of photos.